syslint.com 2015-12-07

# Privacy Policy - Syslint Technologies India Pvt Ltd.

### Privacy Policy

This Privacy Statement describes the ways we collect information from and about you, and what we do with the information, so that you may decide whether or not to provide information to us. Generally, we may collect information about you in two ways:

  * We use automated technical means to collect information about all website visitors; and
  * You may provide information to us via chat, email, telephone calls, web based forms, or other means

The information we collect may include your personal information, such as your name, contact information, financial account numbers, or other things that identify you individually. Please note that this Privacy Statement describes the Syslint commitment to the privacy of persons who are not customers.

##### Disclosure

We do not disclose information about your individual visits with any other company. Information such as your name, address, email address, telephone numbers, etc. are not gathered or used by Real Web Host or any of its partners. We do collect information from website submissions only. This information is limited to your email which is used to confirm submissions or notify of changes to listings that may affect a website within our directory. Syslint may share such information in response to any legal processes, such as a court order, or in special cases such as a physical threat to you or others. Otherwise, this information is kept in secure confidentiality.

##### Information We Collect

We collects certain information from and about its users in three ways:

  * From our web server logs
  * With cookies via forms and
  * Directly from the user

##### Security

We use various security measures to protect the information we collect, as appropriate to the type of information, including encryption, firewalls, and access controls.

##### Sensitive Information

We will not intentionally collect or maintain, and do not want you to provide, any information regarding your medical or health condition, race or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs or other sensitive information.
